http://www.bbrf.org/page/donor-privacy-policy

Home
ResearchIllnessAddictionAnxiety DisordersAttention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD)Bipolar DisorderBorderline Personality Disorder (BPD)Depression.Eating DisordersMental Illness (General)Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder (OCD)Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)SchizophreniaSuicide PreventionOther Brain-Related IllnessesCategoryBasic ResearchNew TechnologiesEarly Intervention/ Diagnostic ToolsNext Generation TherapiesBlogGet InvolvedGiveDonate TodayMemorial/Tribute (make donation)Create Event or Memorial PageFind a Memorial/Tribute PageStock/Securities Donations
/ IRA Charitable RolloversOther Giving OpportunitiesPlanned GivingResearch Partners Donor Advised FundsWorkplace GivingTeam Up for Research!Sponsorship OpportunitiesWatchHealthy Minds TVMeet the Scientists WebinarsVideosConnectAsk the ExpertJoin Us
Home
GrantsGrant FAQsBBRF Young Investigator GrantsBBRF Independent Investigator GrantsBBRF Distinguished Investigator GrantsPrizes & AwardsKlerman & Freedman PrizesOutstanding Achievement PrizesLieber Prize for Schizophrenia ResearchMaltz Prize for Schizophrenia ResearchColvin Prize for Mood Disorders ResearchRuane Prize for Child and Adolescent Psychiatric ResearchGoldman-Rakic Prize for Cognitive Neuroscience ResearchThe Pardes Humanitarian PrizeProductive Lives AwardsBlog
About UsWho We AreOur ImpactFAQsMedia CenterNewsPress ReleasesOpinion PiecesIn the NewsMultimedia LibraryMedia KitEvents & WebinarsTeam Up for Research! EventsHealthy Minds TVContactEmail Signup
Donate
Menu
Donate
Illness
Addiction
Anxiety Disorders
Attention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)
Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD)
Bipolar Disorder
Borderline Personality Disorder (BPD)
Depression
.
Eating Disorders
Mental Illness (General)
Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder (OCD)
Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD)
Schizophrenia
Suicide Prevention
Other Brain-Related Illnesses
Category
Basic Research
New Technologies
Early Intervention/ Diagnostic Tools
Next Generation Therapies
Give
Donate Today
Memorial/Tribute (make donation)
Create Event or Memorial Page
Find a Memorial/Tribute Page
Stock/Securities Donations
/ IRA Charitable Rollovers
Other Giving Opportunities
Planned Giving
Research Partners
Donor Advised Funds
Workplace Giving
Team Up for Research!
Sponsorship Opportunities
Watch
Healthy Minds TV
Meet the Scientists Webinars
Videos
Connect
Ask the Expert
Join Us
Donor Privacy Policy
Donor Privacy Policy
Donor Privacy Policy
We collect no personal information about you without your knowledge when you visit this site, although you may choose to provide this information to us in specific instances. However, we do collect and store certain information automatically:
the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the domain from which you access the Internet (e.g., 123.456.789.012), whether yours individually or provided as a proxy by your Internet Service Provider (ISP)
the date and time you access our site
the pages you visit (recorded by the text and graphics files that compose that page)
the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.
We use the summary statistics to help us make our site more useful to visitors, such as assessing what information is of most and least interest to visitors, and for other purposes such as determining the site's technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas. This information is NOT shared with anyone beyond the support staff for this website, except when required by law enforcement investigation, and is used only as a source of anonymous statistical information.
Please be assured that we have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any personal information we receive from you. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. As with any transmission over the Internet, however, there is always some element of risk involved in sending personal information. In order to try to minimize this risk, we encrypt all information that you submit in conducting a donation using Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology. SSL protects information as it crosses the Internet. This Website has a current Comodo (Cloudflare) Certificate. Information exchanged with any address beginning with https is encrypted using SSL before transmission.
You may contact us should you wish to review or correct any personal information you have chosen to provide our organization.
Donate Now
Donations are welcome
Amount
N/A
$35
$100
$250
$500
Enter your amount
Donate
DONATE
100% of every dollar donated for research is invested in our research grants. Our operating expenses are covered by separate foundation grants.The Brain & Behavior Research Foundation is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization, our Tax ID # is 31-1020010.
